hi I'm Joe Brewer and this is suresh
Fernando we're social entrepreneurs
interested in using collaboration
techniques crowdsourcing and open source
to help solve problems for social
movements now here on rockethub I
recently had the success of launching a
crowdfunding campaign to write a
strategy handbook for the progressive
movement and now that we've launched
that we're wanting to tackle one of the
biggest problems confronting the
movement which is the lack of financial
capital or the lack of money available
to seed long-term investments to help
the movement grow and be sustained over
time so we want to help solve that
problem with this project thanks Joe
thanks for including me in the project
and as you say there is a significant
problem in fact two related problems the
first being the absence or almost
complete lack of funding for early-stage
social innovators those that are trying
to do social good simultaneously with
this there's the general problem of how
you bring about social change and the
inhibitions or the constraints
associated with the existing political
structure Institute corporations etc
fortunately we can sort of address both
of these problems simultaneously by
using crowdsourcing and open
collaboration principles both to raise
funds as well as to coordinate aggregate
mobilize people and so on and so forth
so what we'll try to do is in the work
that we do is to identify existing
models people that are working in this
space as well as propose some new models
both that will address the funding
problem as well as maybe paint a bit of
a picture as to how we didn't organize
and coordinate to move forward together
so that brings us back to this campaign
we want to raise five thousand dollars
in 30 days to help us write a handbook
kind of a how-to guide on how to use
crowdfunding techniques to build social
movements over time so please join us
and help us we really can't do this
without your help thank you